本WEB版外挂字幕由
风吹来的那片云 双语合并
《匹兹堡医魂》 第二季第十五集
巴兰 这是你吗
Baran, is this you?
我五岁那年得了严重的
病毒性脑膜炎后就开始了
It began after a bad case
of viral meningitis when I was five.
他们尝试了所有抗癫痫药物
They tried every anti-seizure medication,
但我还是每隔几个月就会发作
but I still had episodes
every few months or so.
以前从没有人注意到
他们以为我只是在专注思考
No one's ever noticed before.
They just think I'm thoughtful.
你开车吗
Are you driving?
我开不了 直到12年前
I couldn't until laser ablation
做了左颞叶激光消融术
to my left temporal lobe 12 years ago.
那之后再加上开浦兰 我再没发作过
Between that and the Keppra,
I've been seizure-free,
精神科医生认为我可以开车
并担任主治医生
cleared by Neurology to drive
and to work as an attending.
你今天的发作和你上一次发作之间
间隔了多久
How long, uh, between the seizure
you had today and the last one?
一年多
It's been well over a year.
但我今天发作了两次
But I had two today.
我不知道为什么
I don't know why.
可能是因为睡眠不足 新工作的压力 我…
It could be sleep deprivation, new job stress.
从阿富汗回来后
我就没接触过儿科病例了
I--I haven't had to deal
with Peds cases since Afghanistan.
你现在有什么治疗方案
What are your options now?
加大开浦兰药量
up my Keppra
或者试试某种新型抗癫痫药
or maybe try one
of the newer anti-seizure meds.
但如果不管用的话 我只有两个选择
But if that doesn't work,
I'm left with two choices
一个是颞叶切除术
但可能会影响我的语言功能
um, a temporal lobectomy,
which could impair my speech,
另一个是植入神经调节装置
or get a neuromodulation device,
可以感知到癫痫发作并立即阻止
which can sense and stop
the seizures almost immediately.
你必须公开这件事
You need to disclose this.
我知道 我有计划
I know. I have a plan.
嘿 罗比 达娜找你 她在儿科
Hey, Robby, Dana's looking for you.
She's in Peds.
好的 我马上过去
Yeah, OK, I'll be right there.
看来儿科需要你 我也有病人要看
Sounds like you're needed in Peds,
and I have patients to see.
罗比 有一个严重头痛的孕妇
Robby, pregnant woman
with severe headache
被救护车送来的
on her way in by ambulance.
找阿伯特或是夜班住院医生
Find Abbot or a night shift resident.
（第15小时）
（晚上9点至10点）
我需要你清空口袋
Need you to turn out your pockets.
好的 伸出双手
OK. Show me your hands.
经常来这儿吗
Come here often?
怎么了
What's going on?
抱歉 虚惊一场 我们以为她发烧了
Oh, sorry--false alarm.
We thought she spiked a fever,
结果是从那一堆纸质病历里拿错了
but it was the wrong chart
from our analog hell.
你认识愿意接受亲属领养的人吗
You know anybody
who might consider kinship adoption?
- 医生和护士都符合要求 - 别看我
- Doctors and nurses qualify.
- Don't look at me.
嘿 你能让你的人盯着点
阿尔-哈希米医生直到她离开吗
Hey, can your staff keep an eye
on Dr. Al-Hashimi until she leaves?
为什么
Why?
因为她太累了 我不想看到她出错
Uh, because I think she's tired,
and I don't want her to make any mistakes.
好建议 也许也适用于你
Oh, great advice. Maybe you should take it.
是啊 我要出去呼吸下新鲜空气
Yeah. I'm gonna go get some fresh air.
顺便把我的那份也吸了
Grab some for me while you're out there.
你的肺会手足无措的
Your lungs wouldn't know what to do with it.
- 去你的 - 在孩子面前爆粗口 你可真行
- Screw you! - In front of the baby? Nice.
乖
Yeah.
我们是夜行者
We are the night crawlers.
我们处理的是
最奇怪最狂野的病例 因为…
We deal with the weirdest
and the wildest because...
我们是最奇怪最狂野的医生
We are the weirdest
and the wildest of them all.
没错 今晚他们必然会满地乱爬
去拿下他们吧
That is right, and tonight, they are
really gonna be crawling. Now go get some!
抱歉吵醒你了
Sorry to wake you.
我…我在思考呢
I--I was thinking.